eaglenationalmint.com 2008-09-14

# Privacy Policy

Information Collection & Use

Registration  
In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and/or create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

You will also have the option to set your email preferences. These preferences, which can be changed at anytime by the user, tell us how you would like us to contact you. You can control whether you would like to receive our weekly newsletter, special event notification, daily special email, or confirmation of phone orders.

You will receive a confirmation email confirming your registration. Depending on your email preferences, you will receive additional updates and emails. For more information, please review our communications section.

Eagle National Mint is the sole owner of the information collected on eaglenationalmaint.com. Eagle National Mint collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

Orders  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

You will receive a confirmation email confirming your registration as well as order and shipment confirmation. Depending on your email preferences, you will receive additional updates and emails. For more information, please review our communications section.

Tell-A-Friend  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Eagle National Mint stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at [service@eaglenationalmint.com](mailto:service@eaglenationalmint.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

Uses of Information  
Communications from the Site

Special Offers and Updates   
We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page. You can change your email settings by logging into your account. 

Newsletters   
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please change your email notification settings in your account to opt out of email communications.

Customer Service  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

Profile  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third party sources to create a "profile" of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. 

We do not share your profile with other third parties.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
We do link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

Personally identifiable information:  
We Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties 

Agents  
We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

Service Providers  
We use other third parties to provide email notification, site tracking, and affiliate management, on our site. When you sign up for newsletters, sign up as a user, or place an order, we will share name, email address, and order totals only when necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

Other Third Parties

Site Tracking Data  
We share aggregate data about user behaviors in order to generate reporting that allows us to more effectively provide a quality service.

Email Management  
We share email address name, and aggregate order preferences with third party email management services. These services allow us to deliver and track email announcements, and other product data. These service providers are prohibited to share or use any data provided by Eagle National Mint. 

Affiliate Management  
We share aggregate data regarding order amounts in order to support our affiliate program. This data is associated with users cookies but not with personal identifiable information.

Legal Disclaimer  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site

Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference by logging into your account. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by logging into your user account. 

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

Log Files  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses and cookies are tied to personally identifiable information to better identify products and services that our customers are interested in.

Cookies  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.  

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information. 

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see "Choice and Opt-out." 

Third Party Advertisers

We do not use third party advertising on our site.

Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Eagle National Mint. Please be aware that we, Eagle National Mint, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [help@eaglenationalmint.com](mailto:help@eaglenationalmint.com).

Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [help@eaglenationalmint.com](mailto:help@eaglenationalmint.com)

Business Transitions

In the event Eagle National Mint goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

Contact Us   
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [help@eaglenationalmint.com](mailto:help@eaglenationalmint.com)
